vlesociety.com 2017-12-27

# PRIVACY POLICY - Sitapur vle society

The Society for Corporate Governance respects your right to privacy and is committed to protecting your personal information. This Privacy Policy summarizes the practices regarding information collection, use and disclosure practices for this website (vlesociety.com).

WHAT PERSONAL INFORMATION DO WE GATHER?

When you visit our website, you may provide us with two types of information: (a) personal information you knowingly and voluntarily choose to disclose, and (b) information that we automatically collect as you browse our website. We collect and store any information you voluntarily enter on our website or provide to us in offline contacts we have with you. The following information is collected from visitors to our website, as applicable:

REGISTRATION FORMS

If you register for an event or to make a purchase, we will generally ask you to provide contact information and preferences regarding the event or material for which you desire to register. You may, however, visit certain publicly available portions of this website without registering. Other sections are only available to members and require membership and registration.

MEMBERSHIP

Our website’s membership application form requires you to give us your contact information and financial information. We use your contact information to send you information about the Society. Your contact information is also used to contact you when necessary. Financial information that is collected is used to bill you for membership, products and services.

ORDER FORMS

Some areas of this website may allow you to order products or services, whether or not for a fee. In connection with these transactions, we collect data necessary to complete the transaction and that is furnished by you, which may include contact information, date of birth, e-mail address, telephone number and your credit card number.

E-MAIL

On several screens of this website, you have an opportunity to communicate with us by e-mail. You may also choose to provide your e-mail address to receive communications from us or third parties.

AUTOMATICALLY COLLECTED INFORMATION and COOKIES

When you browse our website, you and your web browser may also transmit information that we automatically collect. We do log your IP address (the Internet address of your computer), the webpages you visit and the time of your visit, and other click-stream data. This information may be combined with other personal information you voluntarily have provided. The only other type of information automatically provided to us is the type of computer, operating system and browser you are using. This information is provided by your browser, which we use to improve the performance of this website and make it more compatible with the technology used by the visitors to this website. We may also place small data files, called “cookies”, in the browser file of your computer’s hard drive. These cookies automatically identify your browser to our server whenever you interact with this website. We use the cookies to record website statistics. Most browsers automatically accept the cookies, but you usually can change your browser setting to prevent the acceptance of cookies. Certain webpages may not function properly if you choose not to accept cookies.

HOW DO WE USE YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION?

We use your personal information to communicate with you if and when necessary in connection with your use of this website, to respond to your questions, or to send you material and information you request. We may also use your information to: personalize your website experience and to allow us to deliver the type of content and product information in which you are most interested; consider your suggestions; possibly respond directly to you for clarification; process your request for materials or information; try to answer any questions you may have; and provide you with e-mail messages and other information regarding upcoming events, new services and general information about our products and services. You may elect not to receive these communications, either when you initially register at this website, or at any time thereafter. We may also use collected information in order to help diagnose problems with this website. We may use all information we collect to analyze statistical use patterns and demographic data (basically, where our visitors come from and what demographic characteristics they have) and to improve this website to better serve our customers. We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our servers, and to administer this website. Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart and to gather broad demographic information. We may also prepare and keep statistical records and other data about you and other users of this website, but we do that in a way that does not identify you or any other user personally. We may hire third parties to help us collect and analyze such data, and we may share such statistical data with such affiliated third parties. Again, such statistical data will not specifically identify you or any other user. We use this information to help us make this website more useful to you and other visitors — to learn about the number of visitors to this website, what part of this website visitors are interested in, how long visitors use this website, and the types of technology our visitors use.

DISCLOSING YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION TO OTHERS

Except in the limited circumstances described above and stated in this paragraph, we don’t sell, rent, license, trade or otherwise disclose the personal information of this website’s visitors to unaffiliated third parties. We may disclose your information to third parties who assist us in operating this website or conducting our business. We may disclose information about you if and when we believe it is necessary to comply with any law, rule, court order, or subpoena, or to enforce our legal rights or the rules of this website, or to protect our business, property and operations. Some areas of this website may allow you to conduct e-commerce transactions (event registration, publication purchase, etc.). In connection with these transactions, we collect data necessary to complete the transaction that is furnished by you. This information may be furnished to a third party in order to facilitate the transaction. Your personal information may be transferred to another entity (either an affiliated entity or an unrelated third party) in connection with a merger, reorganization, dissolution or similar corporate event. If such a transfer were ever to occur, the acquiring entity’s use of your personal information will still be subject to this Privacy Policy.

LINKS TO OTHER SITES

We may create links to other websites that we think may be of interest to you. We do not endorse any other websites, and this Privacy Policy applies only to your use of our website. We have not reviewed the privacy policies of any websites we link to this website, and you should read the privacy policies of each website you visit to determine what information about you that website may collect and use.

SECURITY

Because we are committed to your privacy, we have put in place physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to attempt to safeguard and help prevent unauthorized access, maintain data security, and correctly use the personal information we collect online. When you place an order or access your personal information on this website, we offer the use of a secure server. However, please remember that no transmission of data over the Internet or any wireless network can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant the security of any information that you transmit to us or from us, and you do so at your own risk.

CHANGES IN OUR PRIVACY POLICY

By using this website, you consent to our collection and the use of your personal information as described in this Privacy Policy. If we change our Privacy Policy, we will post these changes on this website. You have the opportunity to review this Privacy Policy each time you use this website so that you are aware of any modifications made to these policies.

CHOICE/OPT OUT

Our website provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us. You have the option of reviewing or removing your information from our database, and to no longer receive communication from us. If you are a member, you can express your communication preferences on your personal account page on our website and you may unsubscribe from e-mails by clicking the unsubscribe link at the bottom of a received email. If you wish to have your account information deleted from our database, please send an e-mail.

Note that we may maintain information about individual sales transactions for the purpose of recordkeeping and servicing.

QUESTIONS ABOUT OUR PRIVACY POLICY

If you have questions about our website or our Privacy Policy, please feel free to [email](http://www.vlesociety.com/contact-us/).
